https://www.polkadotdesign.com/customer-care/security-privacy-policy/

holidayholidayvalentines day suppliesmardi grasst. patricks dayeastercinco de mayomemorial day4th of julynational night outhalloweenthanksgivingchristmasnew years cards 2021hanukkah suppliesphoto cardsphoto cardsbirth announcement photo cardsbirthday photo cardschristmas photo cardsgraduation photo cardshanukkah photo cardsnew year photo cardssave the date photo cardsmulti shaped photo cardsthanksgiving photo cardsinvitationsinvitationsafrican american invitationsbirthday invitationsgraduation invitationsparty invitationspolka dot invitationspre-wedding partiesreligious celebrationssuper bowl partyquinceaneraannouncementsannouncementsbirth announcement cardsgraduation announcementsmoving announcementssave the datesbaby & kidbaby & kidtwin baby shower invitationsbaby shower invitationskids birthday invitationsbirth announcementsreligious party invitationsweddingweddingpre wedding party invitationswedding stationerybridal shower invitationsengagement party invitationsrehearsal invitationsbridal luncheon invitationswedding save the dateswedding invitationswedding essentialsstationerystationeryafrican american stationeryback to school suppliespersonalized stationerythank you cardsaddress labelsgift tags & stickerscalling cardsnotepadscalendar padsrecipe cardsresponse & enclosure cardsparty ideasparty ideasbeach party ideasbig rig party ideasbowling party ideasdinosaur party ideasgymnastics party ideaslaser tag party ideasluau party ideasmermaid party ideaspirate party ideaspool party ideasprincess party ideasskate party ideassoccer party ideastea party ideasgiftgiftcalendar pads giftsenclosure cards giftsmonograms giftsnotepads giftspersonalized stamperspersonalized stationery giftsrecipe cards giftsgift guideshop by brandshop by brandfresh presskristen alexanderodd ballspolka dot designpsa essentialsstevie streckclearance
Login View Basket Search Customer Care Contact service@polkadotdesign.com 877.816.0884 Ideas Typestyles Flourishes Wording Ideas Theme Party Ideas Printing Tips Photo Tips
holidayholidayvalentines day suppliesmardi grasst. patricks dayeastercinco de mayomemorial day4th of julynational night outhalloweenthanksgivingchristmasnew years cards 2021hanukkah suppliesphoto cardsphoto cardsbirth announcement photo cardsbirthday photo cardschristmas photo cardsgraduation photo cardshanukkah photo cardsnew year photo cardssave the date photo cardsmulti shaped photo cardsthanksgiving photo cardsinvitationsinvitationsafrican american invitationsbirthday invitationsgraduation invitationsparty invitationspolka dot invitationspre-wedding partiesreligious celebrationssuper bowl partyquinceaneraannouncementsannouncementsbirth announcement cardsgraduation announcementsmoving announcementssave the datesbaby & kidbaby & kidtwin baby shower invitationsbaby shower invitationskids birthday invitationsbirth announcementsreligious party invitationsweddingweddingpre wedding party invitationswedding stationerybridal shower invitationsengagement party invitationsrehearsal invitationsbridal luncheon invitationswedding save the dateswedding invitationswedding essentialsstationerystationeryafrican american stationeryback to school suppliespersonalized stationerythank you cardsaddress labelsgift tags & stickerscalling cardsnotepadscalendar padsrecipe cardsresponse & enclosure cardsparty ideasparty ideasbeach party ideasbig rig party ideasbowling party ideasdinosaur party ideasgymnastics party ideaslaser tag party ideasluau party ideasmermaid party ideaspirate party ideaspool party ideasprincess party ideasskate party ideassoccer party ideastea party ideasgiftgiftcalendar pads giftsenclosure cards giftsmonograms giftsnotepads giftspersonalized stamperspersonalized stationery giftsrecipe cards giftsgift guideshop by brandshop by brandfresh presskristen alexanderodd ballspolka dot designpsa essentialsstevie streckclearanceMy Account | Customer Care NEED A COUPON CODE? CLICK HERE FOR THE LATEST POLKA DOT DESIGN PROMOTION CODES.
Polka Dot Design
>
Customer Care
>
Security and Privacy Policy
Security and Privacy Policy
Security
Polka Dot Design goes to great lengths to protect your personal information. This includes secure servers and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. Our SSL is provided by AlphaSSL, a trusted leader in online security services. We are also a verified merchant with Authorize.Net.
Our Commitment to Privacy
Polka Dot Design appreciates the growing need for protecting the privacy of our customers' personal information, and such protection is our priority. We make certain that any information provided to us is secure. The strictest means of security are in place to safeguard against potential threats. To continue serving you best, we have supplied the following notification of what personal information is collected and how it will be used.
What kind of information does Polka Dot Design collect?
When you register with Polka Dot Design, we collect and store your email address and a secret password. This information is used to create an individual account for you. Inside your account, you have access to view your online proof for approval to print, your order history, along with receipts, shipping and tracking information. Other information is collected so that we may process your order - this includes billing and shipping address, and your contact telephone number and email address. Polka Dot Design will not sell, share or rent any information to third parties. When you personalize a product, we will ask you for information needed to complete your order. This information may include your name, type of event, date of event, R.S.V.P. telephone number, and event address. This information is only available to the registered user via their online account.
Will you share my information with third parties?
Polka Dot Design will not sell, share or rent any information to third parties, other than what is disclosed within this privacy statement. Some products are shipped to our customers directly from the manufacturers. Shipping information may be passed to our manufacturers for orders that are shipped directly from the manufacturer to the customer. This information is only utilized in fulfilling orders. Click here to see a listing of our manufacturers and their locations.
When will Polka Dot Design contact me?
Polka Dot Design will contact you by email once your order is placed through a series of automatically generated messages. All orders will receive an order confirmation email once the order is submitted and will receive a shipment notification email with tracking information when the order is shipped. Additionally, custom printed orders that receive a proof will receive automatic messages with proofing instructions and proof notifications each time a new proof is uploaded. Polka Dot Design will also contact you by telephone or email if we have any questions regarding your order, such as verifying your billing or shipping address, confirming your custom print options, notifying you of a backordered item or to obtain any additional information that will aid in the processing of your order.
We may also contact you by email about our products, services, contests and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communication.
How do I access or change my information?
You can change your contact telephone number, email address, password and billing information through your online account. You can also become a member of our website and receive occasional information on products, services and special promotions. If you prefer not to receive special information from us, you have the option to take yourself off our mailing list. You may also unsubscribe yourself by sending us an email and write unsubscribe in the subject box.
How does Polka Dot Design use cookies?
Our websites use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our website and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience.
You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, however, you will not be able to access your account information or make purchases on our website.
How do I know my credit card and personal information are secure?
Polka Dot Design goes to great lengths to protect your personal information. This includes secure servers and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. McAfee SECURE also tests our site daily for security vulnerabilities.
How do I contact you?
For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update your personal information, or to place an order, you can contact us by telephone, 877.816.0884 or by email, orders@polkadotdesign.com.
CUSTOMER CARE:
Orders outside the U.S.A.
CUSTOMER CARE:
Orders outside the U.S.A.
